<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="service.subtitles.a4ksubtitles"
       name="a4kSubtitles"
       version="2.8.0"
       provider-name="Unknown">
    <requires>
      <import addon="script.module.requests"/>
      <import addon="vfs.libarchive" optional="true"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.subtitle.module" library="main.py"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="main_service.py" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en">a4kSubtitles - Multi-Source Subtitles Addon</summary>
        <description>
Multi-source subtitles addon optimized for Seren and a4kScrapers.
Supports: OpenSubtitles, BSPlayer, Podnadpisi.NET, Subscene, Addic7ed
        </description>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <reuselanguageinvoker>true</reuselanguageinvoker>
        <license>MIT License</license>
        <website>https://github.com/newt-sc/a4kSubtitles</website>
        <source>https://github.com/newt-sc/a4kSubtitles</source>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <screenshot>screenshot-01.png</screenshot>
            <screenshot>screenshot-02.png</screenshot>
            <screenshot>screenshot-03.png</screenshot>
        </assets>
        <news>
[v2.8.0]:
  * Support tvshows with more than 250 episodes for episode id lookup when tvshow imdb id is provided.

[v2.7.0]:
  * Support tvshow imdb id, along with season and episode passed from video file url.

[v2.6.0]:
  * Support imdb id (movie or episode) passed from video file url.

[v2.5.0]:
  * Add TLS adapter fallback

[v2.4.0]:
  * Fix some ssl issues

[v2.3.0]:
  * Add concurrency error handling

[v2.2.0]:
  * Fix KODI 19 Matrix support

[v2.1.0]:
  * Fix Persian search in Subscene

[v2.0.0]:
  * Use IMDb as main source for all meta.
  * Retry on 503 (Service Unavailable). OpenSubtitles and Subscene seems to return it occasionally.

[v1.8.0]:
  * Remove SubDb (Site is down)
  * Make lib vfs optional since there are fallbacks and it is used as last case scenario. Thus making the addon installable on platforms which are not supported by lib vfs.

[v1.7.2]:
  * Improve results sort based on title match

[v1.7.1]:
  * Drop python meta as it prevents installations on pre Kodi 19 versions

[v1.7.0]:
  * Update python meta to enable Kodi 19 installations

[v1.6.0]:
  * Add option to auto download first subtitle result silently

[v1.5.0]:
  * Auto open search dialog only on movie and tvshow videos

[v1.4.0]:
  * Add option to auto open the search dialog when the video does not have subtitles

[v1.3.0]:
  * Improve tvshow year scraping

[v1.2.0]:
  * Use internal ZipFile for extraction with a fallback to vfs.libarchive

[v1.1.0]:
  * Improve imdb id scraping

[v1.0.1]:
  * Add screenshots

[v1.0.0]:
  * Invalidate BSPlayer results cache when download links expire
  * Extraction fallback: zip -> gzip -> raw

[v0.0.30]:
  * Add service names in ad detection
  * Removed the option to disable cleaning of ads
  * Add remote fetching of addic7ed data

[v0.0.29]:
  * Fix Podnadpisi download of results missing filename meta
  * Fix last results cache not invalidated on language preferences change

[v0.0.28]:
  * Attempt scrape of imdb id when missing
  * Improve filename parsing
  * Fix SubDB lang code
  * Fix Podnadpisi not returning release name

[v0.0.27]:
  * Attempt to auto-fix a garbled cyrillic encoded subtitles
  * Fix more encoding issues
  * Ensure progress dialog close even if the addon crashes
  * Apply color to service name in results and bold tags
  * Show notification if imdb id is missing

[v0.0.26]:
  * Support for Addic7ed
  * Improve cache of the last results
  * Don't show progress when showing results from cache

[v0.0.25]:
  * Fix cancellation thread exit

[v0.0.24]:
  * Show progress dialog only for search

[v0.0.23]:
  * Add progress dialog
  * Support cancellation

[v0.0.22]:
  * Fix meta string conversion issue

[v0.0.21]:
  * TVShow year scrape from imdb when necessary

[v0.0.20]:
  * Improve Subscene tvshow matching
  * Extract first sub file from zips when none is matched
  * Fix Podnadpisi not working properly for tvshows
  * Fix non-ascii video file title issues
  * Add tvshow tests

[v0.0.19]:
  * Update settings
  * Fix language code suffix format in the subtitle file name
  * Support for Subscene

[v0.0.18]:
  * Support for Podnadpisi.NET
  * Support for SubDB

[v0.0.17]:
  * Reuse KODI's Python language invoker
    * Improves performance on low-end devices when switching subtitles for best match
  * Url decode subtitle names

[v0.0.16]:
  * Cache last result
  * OpenSubtitles always queries:
    * by imdb id and title
    * by video file hash
  * Improve results ordering:
    * preferred lang
    * lang
    * synced
    * name match
    * rating
    * hearing impaired
    * subtitle service
  * Fix url with numbers matching in ads detection

[v0.0.15]:
  * Remove ads by default
  * Support for BSPlayer
  * Additional option for OpenSubtitles to use file hash (Limits results to exact matches)

[v0.0.14]:
  * Fix API and normal usage at the same time

[v0.0.13]:
  * Exclude development files from release

[v0.0.12]:
  * Removal of ads (Experimental)
  * Fix extract issue when file contains unicode symbols

[v0.0.11]:
  * Changelog in KODI

[v0.0.10]:
  * Inserted language code in sub filename

[v0.0.9]:
  * Implemented (orginal, default, none, forced_only) as KODI language setting
  * Fixed minor bugs in API implementation
  * Added .idea folder to .gitignore

[v0.0.8]:
  * opensubtitles should make max 2 requests for separate languages
  * lint updates
  * add tests for download

[v0.0.7]:
  * API class rename

[v0.0.6]:
  * fix core requiring handle even with API usage

[v0.0.5]:
  * expose API for usage without KODI
  * add tests for search

[v0.0.4]:
  * distribution process:
    * KODI repository with updates based on github releases
    * addons.xml and addons.xml.crc auto generation via git hooks
    * release automation on merge to master via Github Actions

[v0.0.3]:
  * general settings for configuring requests timeout and results limit
  * additional ordering of the results depending on the similarity ratio of the video file name and the subtitle file name

[v0.0.2]:
  * improve archive extraction support
  * limit the results and add requests timeout
  * fix OpenSubtitles authentication
  * handle debug logging detection issues

[v0.0.1]:
  * initial working version (search and download subtitles)
  * OpenSubtitles support with optional authentication
  * results ordering with preferred language ordered first
        </news>
    </extension>
</addon>
